Contact

kamccoy22@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kaseymccoy (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Medical-Surgical
Oncology Nursing
Infusion Centers

Languages

English

Kasey McCoy

Team Lead at St. Joseph's/Candler Georgia Infirmary

Greater Savannah Area

Summary

Seventeen years of professional clinical nurse experience in various settings including inpatient and outpatient hospital, & home health care settings

Seventeen years of proven dedication and excellence in providing quality, patient-centered care

Organized, self-motivated, and strong ability to adapt to changing policies and procedures

Proven ability to work as a team with multidisciplinary staff to produce immediate results for the patient

Experience

St. Joseph's/Candler Team Leader, Adult Day Health March 2020 - Present (6 months) Savannah, Georgia, United States

Supervises nursing and is accountable for the provision of consistent, quality care.

Hire Dynamics
Agency Nurse
March 2020 - April 2020 (2 months)
Savannah, Georgia, United States

Medical Field Seeking employment in Case Management October 2019 - March 2020 (6 months) Savannah, Georgia Area

Motivated Registered Nurse seeking Employment in the field of Case Management.

Department of Juvenile Justice Registered Nurse April 2017 - August 2019 (2 years 5 months)

Seeking Employment or Consulting Opportunities RN

December 2015 - April 2017 (1 year 5 months)

Savannah, Georgia Area

Humana at Home Nurse Care Manager April 2016 - July 2016 (4 months)

Metroplex Hospital Registered Nurse June 2011 - July 2015 (4 years 2 months) Killeen, TX

Cardiac Unit/Medical-Surgical Unit

Sentara Careplex Hospital Infusion Nurse April 2010 - March 2011 (1 year) Hampton, VA

Outpatient Infusion Center

Maxim Healthcare Services
Registered Nurse
October 2009 - March 2010 (6 months)
Newport News, VA

Private Duty Nursing, Flu and Wellness Clinics

Greenwood Regional Rehabilitation Hospital Registered Nurse May 2008 - March 2009 (11 months) Greenwood, SC

Self Regional Healthcare charge nurse June 2002 - May 2008 (6 years) Greenwood, SC

Oncology/Medical unit

Education

Lander University
BSN, Nursing Science · (1998 - 2002)

Strom Thurmond High School (1994 - 1998)